OK, so now let's attack the fun issue.
حسنًا، لنتطرق الآن إلى المشكلة الممتعة.
You're really going to feel like magicians after this.
ستشعرون حقًا بمدى براعتكم بعدها.
We will need to identify all of the records in
سنحتاج إلى تحديد جميع السجلات
the start date column that have as soon as possible,
في عمود تاريخ البدء الذي يحتوي على في أسرع وقت ممكن،
immediately and such somehow,
وعلى الفور، وما إلى ذلك،
then we need to replace the text and all of those cells with ASAP.
ثم علينا استخدام ASAP بدلًا من النص وجميع هذه الخلايا.
What are the other versions of this though?
ما الإصدارات الأخرى من ذلك؟
Let's take a look at the most common start dates using
لنلقِ نظرة على تواريخ البدء الأكثر شهرة باستخدام
Pandas' value counts function on the start dates column in DF clean data frame.
دالة عدد القيمة لـ Pandas في عمود تاريخ البدء في إطار البيانات DF clean.
Value counts as one of the programmatic assessments that we covered previously.
القيمة هي أحد التقييمات البرمجية التي تطرقنا لها فيما سبق.
OK, so immediately, as soon as possible, immediate, immediate employment,
حسنًا، إن على الفور، وفي أقرب وقت ممكن، وفورًا، وتوظيف فوري،
as soon as possible with a period,
وفي أقرب وقت في خلال مدة،
immediate job opportunity, these all seem similar in spirit to as soon as possible to me.
وفرصة عمل فورية، تبدو جميعًا مشابهة لأقرب وقت ممكن.
And there are actually a ton more,
ويوجد العديد من ذلك،
which is conveyed through this ellipsis here.
ويتم نقلها عن طريق علامة الحذف هذه.
You can actually expand these results here
يمكنكم زيادة هذه النتائج هنا حقًا
and check for all of the similar phrases yourself.
والتحقق من جميع هذه العبارات المتشابهة بأنفسكم.
But I did some legwork preparing for this class,
لكنني قمت بجمع بعض المعلومات للتحضير لهذا الدرس،
and found it listed every value similar in
ووجدت أنها تدرج جميع القيم المتشابهة
spirit for your convenience, which I'll paste here.
لتوفير الراحة لكم، وسأقوم بلصقها هنا.
You're going to have to do this dirty work
ستضطرون إلى القيام بهذا العمل الرديء
yourself when you go out wrangling on your own.
بأنفسكم عندما تتخلصون من الأعمال المتعارضة بأنفسكم.
So keep this in mind. OK. So let's convert all of these to ASAP.
لذا يُرجى مراعاة ذلك. حسنًا. لنحوِّل جميع هذه القيم إلى ASAP.
We're going to have to test each entry in
سنختبر كل إدخال في
the start date column for a match with every item in this list.
عمود تاريخ البدء لمطابقته مع كل عنصر في هذه القائمة.
Then replace the ones that do match with ASAP.
ثم استخدموا ASAP بهذه العناصر.
Note that the items in this list need to be strings,
لاحظوا أن العناصر الموجودة في هذه القائمة تحتاج إلى أن تكون سلاسل،
because the datatype of the start date column is string,
لأن نوع بيانات عمود تاريخ البدء عبارة عن سلسلة،
also known as object in Pandas.
ويُعرف أيضًا باسم الكائن في Pandas.
T type or O object.
يشير الحرف T إلى النوع أو O إلى الكائن.
OK, so let's hop on Google again and see how Pandas can help us out here.
حسنًا، لننتقل إلى Google مرة أخرى ونرى كيف يمكن أن يساعدنا Pandas هنا.
OK, so Pandas replace values in series.
حسنًا، يستبدل Pandas القيم الموجودة في السلسلة.
A series is also known as a column in a Pandas data frame.
تُعرف السلسلة أيضًا باسم عمود في إطار البيانات Pandas.
And we want to replace values in the start date column or start date series.
ونريد استبدال القيم الموجودة في عمود تاريخ البدء أو سلسلة تاريخ البدء.
So this first search result here is actually what you're going to use,
حسنًا، إن ما سنستخدمه في الواقع هو نتيجة البحث الأولى هنا،
but there are lots of ways of accomplishing this task in Pandas.
لكن هناك العديد من الطرق لإنجاز هذه المهمة في Pandas.
But this is the most straightforward.
لكن هذه الطريق هي الأكثر سهولة.
So Panda's dot series dot replace.
نقطة السلسلة نقطة استبدال في Panda.
OK, so the data replace function operates on a Pandas series and it replaces values
حسنًا، تعمل دالة استبدال البيانات على سلسلة Pandas وهي تستبدل القيم
given in to replace where the first parameter with value or the second parameter.
الموضحة لاستخدام القيمة أو المعلمة الثانية محل المعلمة الاولى.
One more thing to keep in mind is this in-place parameter here.
الشيء الآخر الذي يجب وضعه في الاعتبار هو المعلمة الموضعية هنا.
The default for in-place is false.
القيمة الافتراضية للمعلمة الموضعية هي خطأ.
We're actually going to convert this to true.
في الواقع سنقوم بتحويلها إلى صحيح.
So we can just minimize our code.
يمكننا تصغير الكود.
You'll see how it works in a second.
سترون كيفية عمل ذلك في ثانية.
OK, let's get this in our Jupyter Notebook.
حسنًا، لندخلها في تطبيق Jupyter Notebook.
and df_clean.StartDate is
وdf_clean.StartDate
our series and we want to use dot replace on this series.
سلسلتنا ونرغب في استخدام نقطة استبدال في هذه السلسلة.
In-place true means that we can just write this line of code
تعني القيمة الموضعية أننا نتمكن من كتابة هذا السطر من الكود
here and execute it and the changes it makes will be reflected in D.F clean.
هنا وتنفيذه، ثم ستظهر التغييرات التي سيجريها في إطار بيانات نظيف.
If there was no inplace true here,
إذا لم يكن هناك قيمة موضعية صحيحة هنا،
we would have to reassign the results of this function to our start date column.
سيجب علينا إعادة تعيين نتائج هذه الدالة إلى عمود تاريخ البدء لدينا.
OK so because there are so many phrases similar to ASAP,
حسنًا، نظرًا لوجود العديد من العبارات المشابهة لـ ASAP،
we are going to need to use a for loop to minimize code repetition,
سنحتاج إلى استخدام تكرار حلقي لتقليل تكرار الكود،
with the body of the for loop being this dot replace function.
ويكون النص الأصلي للتكرار الحلقي دالة نقطة استبدال هذه.
The rest of this code is your task in the upcoming quiz.
إكمال الجزء المتبقي من هذا الكود هو مهمتكم في الاختبار التالي.
Write a for loop and fill out the parameters in this line of code here to replace
عليكم كتابة التكرار الحلقي وملء المعلمات الموجودة في هذا السطر من الكود هنا لاستخدام
every phrase similar in spirit to ASAP with ASAP.
ASAP مكان أي عبارة مشابهة لـ ASAP.